#### **Sneha Tarkar**

Mobile: +91 9137001934

Mail: ms.neha2524@gmail.com

**Total Years of Experience: 9 years** 

**Current Location: Mumbai** 

**Location Preference : Mumbai** 

## **Summary:-**

Highly qualified Operations Coordinator with 9 years of experience being responsible for planning, directing or coordinating one or more administrative services. These included records and information management, mail distribution, facilities planning and maintenance, custodial operations and other office support services.

#### **About Me:-**

Seeking a position as a Operation Coordinator in initiatives that utilize state-of-the-art, software and/or hardware components with a creative, technology-driven organization in an environment that encourages innovative thinking, recognition and career development.

## **Education**

Start – End	Examination	Institution
Sept 2011 - Aug 2014	Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science	Pillai Hoc College.
Sept 2007- July 2011	Diploma of Engineering in Computer Science	Naval Institute Technology
June 2006 - March 2007	S.S.C	Pune Vidya Bhawan

### **Skills & Competencies**

Team Leadership

- Strategic Planning
- Technical Support
- Sorting and labelling
- Mail management
- Administrative Skills

### **Employment History**

Duration	Empl. Name	Job Title	City
17 August 2021 till now	Inventys Research Pvt Ltd	Operation Specialist Coordinator	Kurla
7 July 2017 to 25July 2021	Precimax Engineer Ltd, Ghansoli	Operation Coordinator	Ghansoli
11 Sept 2014 to 16 June 2017	Electronics & Engineering Pvt Ltd	Coordinator Executive	Andheri

# Responsibilities

### **Inventys Research Pvt Ltd**

- Improve operational management systems, processes and best practices
- Purchase materials, plan inventory and oversee warehouse efficiency
- Help the organizations processes remain legally compliant
- Formulate strategic and operational objectives
- Examine financial data and use them to improve profitability
- Manage budgets and forecasts
- Find ways to increase quality of customer service
- Coordinate the activities of regulatory, purchase, logistics and other related departments
- Creating and issuing invoices to customers.
- Following up on outstanding payments and answering customer queries.
- Monitoring all payments and preparing monthly billing reports.
- Providing administrative support as needed.
- Ensure all operations are carried on in an appropriate, cost-effective way
- Maintaining and monitoring project plans, project schedules, work hours, budgets, and expenditures.
- Organizing, attending, and participating in stakeholder meetings.
- Documenting and following up on important actions and decisions from meetings.
- · Preparing necessary presentation materials for meetings.
- Providing administrative support as needed.
- Developing strategies.

#### **Precimax Engineer Ltd**

- Coordinating workflow for all company departments
- Supervising the operations team
- Ensuring the accuracy of supply orders
- Analyzing workflows and activities and looking for ways to improve efficiency

- Tracking and reporting a company's operations performance
- Making operations recommendations to improve efficiency and workflows
- · Managing company inventory and ordering supplies as needed
- · Communicating with external stakeholders

# **Electronics & Engineering Pvt Ltd**

- Coordinate the activities of staff members by effectively and efficiently handling scheduling and work assignment duties
- Supervise daily operations of all departments including order generation, help desk functions, mail pickup, and delivery and shipping and receiving
- Coordinate the logistical details of projects to ensure on-time project delivery
- Ensure that all staff members are working in compliance with the company's procedures and protocols
- Identify problems in operations processes and ensure that they are resolved in a time-efficient manner
- Maintain accurate operations materials and documents for reference purposes
- Monitor and assess daily financial operations and performance management processes
- Coordinate activities with procurement managers to ensure the delivery of supplies and equipment in a time-efficient manner
- Assist with budget planning activities and ensure that any needed modifications are appropriately incorporated
- Plan and schedule projects in a proactive manner by interacting with both external agencies and organizations.
- Ensure that multiple projects meet their projected deadlines effectively.
- Work with human resources staff to develop and monitor the consistency of labor strategies
- Assisting with the management of daily operational activities.
- Coordinating the proper allocation of human resources.
- Arranging and assisting with the onboarding of new employees.
- Handles logistical responsibilities, includes Dispatching documents (domestic + International)
- Maintain procedural documentation for reference purposes.
- Support day-to-day coordination of operational activities.

#### **Personal Details**

Date of Birth: 23rd July 1990

Address : Chembur (Harbor line)